<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>karpurgauram</title>
      <link>https://pratyabhijna.exozy.me</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on karpurgauram</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>•~• Welcome Note •~•</title>
    <link>https://pratyabhijna.exozy.me/</link>
    <guid>https://pratyabhijna.exozy.me/</guid>
    <description>...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 03:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Spanda</title>
    <link>https://pratyabhijna.exozy.me/Spanda/Spanda</link>
    <guid>https://pratyabhijna.exozy.me/Spanda/Spanda</guid>
    <description>]■[ “Spanda System.” ]■[ ⎯ The fourth system, which comprises the Trika philosophy, is called the Spanda system. The word spanda means “movement.” “The Spanda school recognizes that nothing can exist without movement.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 17:05:13 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Krama</title>
    <link>https://pratyabhijna.exozy.me/Krama/Krama</link>
    <guid>https://pratyabhijna.exozy.me/Krama/Krama</guid>
    <description>]■[ “Krama System.” ]■[ ⎯ The Krama system does not recognize the ways of either the Pratyabhijna or the Kula system. In the Krama system, you must rise in succession, step by step.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 17:04:39 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Kula</title>
    <link>https://pratyabhijna.exozy.me/Kula/Kula</link>
    <guid>https://pratyabhijna.exozy.me/Kula/Kula</guid>
    <description>]■[ “Kula System.” ]■[ ⎯ The Kula system teaches you how you can live in caitanya (universal Consciousness), the real nature of yourself, in the act of ascending and descending ...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 17:04:08 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Pratyabhijñā</title>
    <link>https://pratyabhijna.exozy.me/Pratyabhijna/Pratyabhij%C3%B1%C4%81</link>
    <guid>https://pratyabhijna.exozy.me/Pratyabhijna/Pratyabhij%C3%B1%C4%81</guid>
    <description>]■[ “Pratyabhijna System.” ]■[ ⎯ The word pratyabhijna means “to spontaneously once again recognize and realize your Self.” Here you have only to realize, you do not have to practice ...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 17:03:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>test</title>
    <link>https://pratyabhijna.exozy.me/test</link>
    <guid>https://pratyabhijna.exozy.me/test</guid>
    <description>First heading This is a sample document. Index.md is a first page which is our homepage. INFO Press Ctrl + - to zoom out and see full site We can add other things at later thats second heading with two hashes Then, in your terminal of choice, enter the following commands line by line: echo &quot;Welcome to Tantra loka&quot; this is how you add code This could be our index or so this is how we link another pages no matter where they located at but they should have accurate file name [[first page]] [[second page]] [[third page]] first page second page third page ganapati This is how we add external link Video Link [Video Link](www.youtube.com/watch) also images can be added via adding full url of it like above or uploading image file in some folder and giving path like this ![image alt text](/images/shiva.jpg) lists first thing second thing third thing hasttags Hashtags works like wonders here.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 16:49:44 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>ganapati</title>
    <link>https://pratyabhijna.exozy.me/ganapati</link>
    <guid>https://pratyabhijna.exozy.me/ganapati</guid>
    <description>Shri Ganesh असूरसूरवृन्दवन्दितमभिमतवरवितरणे निरतम्। दर्शनशताग्र्यपूज्यं प्राणतनुं गणपतिं वन्दे॥ my first adoration to the lotus-feets of GAṆAPATI; the master of śiva’s servants; ...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 16:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>